<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Le blog de Christian-Nils on Le blog de Christian-Nils</title>
    <link>http://www.christian-nils.se/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Le blog de Christian-Nils on Le blog de Christian-Nils</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 10:00:01 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with MM7150 and Raspberry Pi (software side)</title>
      <link>http://www.christian-nils.se/blog/post/mm7150software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 10:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.christian-nils.se/blog/post/mm7150software/</guid>
      <description>Acknowledgements First of all, I would like to thank Benjamin Tissoires, for his huge help on getting the MM7150 working with my Raspberry Pi. It was the first time for me to go in the Linux kernel and his help was very valuable especially that he is the original author of the i2c-hid driver.
Introduction In this guide, you will find everything you need, software-side, to make your MM7150 work with your Raspberry Pi version 3 (it may work with previous versions).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with MM7150 and Raspberry Pi (hardware implementation)</title>
      <link>http://www.christian-nils.se/blog/post/mm7150hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 10:38:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.christian-nils.se/blog/post/mm7150hardware/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you are on this page, it is because you are interested in using an incredibly cheap 9-axis IMU which offers sensor fusion. The MM7150 was released in 2015 and is available for less than $30. This IMU includes a gyroscope, a magnetometer and an accelerometer. Thanks to the sensor fusion, we are expecting a low error in drift and, additionally to the measures from the sensors, the rotation is expected to be calculated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
